[
  {
    "id": "part6_001",
    "title": "Training Course Email",
    "content": "Questions 1 through 4. refer to the following e-mail.  \n\nTo: Project Leads \n\nFrom: James pak \n\nSubject: Training Courses \n\nTo all Pak Designs project leader: \n\nIn the coming weeks, we will be organizing several training session for __1.__ employees. At Pak Designs, we believe that with the proper help and support from our senior project leaders, less experienced staff can quickly __2.__ a deep understanding of the design process. __3.__, they can improve their ability to communicate effectively across divisions. When employees at all experience levels interact, every employee's competency level rises and the business overall benefits. For that reason, we are urging experienced project leaders to attend each one of the interactive seminars that will be held throught the coming month. __4.__. \n\nThank you for your support. \n\nJames Pak \n\nPak Designs",
    "questions": [
    {
        "question": "blank 1",
        "option": {
          "A": "interest",
          "B": "interests",
          "C": "interested",
          "D": "interesting"
        },
        "answer": "B"
      },
      {
        "question": "blank 2",
        "option": {
          "A": "develop",
          "B": "develop",
          "C": "open",
          "D": "complete"
        },
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "question": "blank 3",
        "option": {
          "A": "After all",
          "B": "For",
          "C": "Even so",
          "D": "At the same time"
        },
        "answer": "D"
      },
      {
        "question": "blank 4",
        "option": {
          "A": "Let me explain our plans for on-site staff training.",
          "B": "We hope that you will strongly consider joining us.",
          "C": "Todayâ€™s training session will be postponed until Monday.",
          "D": "This is the first in a series of such lectures."
        },
        "answer": "B"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "part6_002",
    "title": "Call for Participants Notice",
    "content": "Questions 1 through 4. refer to the following notice.  \n\nAre you an amateur athlete looking for a __1.__? Get ready for the premier competition of the year. Test yor abilites at the Johannesburg Metropolitan Meet of Champions. __2.__ athletes from Randburg. Roodepoort and Sandton will have a chance to represent their hometowns and compete for prizes in a variety of sports .The meet will take place in Roodepoort on 30 March. __3.__. To register,visit jmmchampions.co.za. __4.__ athletes are not eligible to participate in the competitions but may register as volunteers for the event.",
    "questions": [
    {
        "question": "blank 1",
        "option": {
          "A": "trainer",
          "B": "scholarship",
          "C": "teammate",
          "D": "challenge"
        },
        "answer": "D"
      },
      {
        "question": "blank 2",
        "option": {
          "A": "with",
          "B": "yet",
          "C": "where",
          "D": "along"
        },
        "answer": "C"
      },
      {
        "question": "blank 3",
        "option": {
          "A": "Tickes are available at all locations.",
          "B": "It is open to athletes 15 years and older.",
          "C": "Winner will be announced then.",
          "D": "Training is scheduled for the next day."
        },
        "answer": "B"
      },
      {
        "question": "blank 4",
        "option": {
          "A": "Profession",
          "B": "Professional",
          "C": "Professions",
          "D": "Professionally"
        },
        "answer": "B"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "part6_003",
    "title": "Wedding Services Notice",
    "content": "Questions 1 through 4. refer to the following notice.  \n\nEstablished in 1922, the Royal Gardens Reception Ceter offers a choice of two stunning dining rooms for the ultimate wedding experience. The Palace Court features seating for up to 120 guests, __1.__ the Crown Court caters to weddings of up to 240 guests. The Reception Center also features a large rose garden and ornamental lake that provide the perfect backdrop for wedding photographs. __2.__. Our experienced team of five-star __3.__ and professional catering staff will create and serve a custom feast that will impress every one of your guests. So, for the most romantic wedding __4.__, call the Royal Gardens Reception Center. Book early to avoid disappointment.",
    "questions": [
    {
        "question": "blank 1",
        "option": {
          "A": "while",
          "B": "because",
          "C": "otherwise",
          "D": "instead of "
        },
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "question": "blank 2",
        "option": {
          "A": "The course includes five dishes and a dessert.",
          "B": "The garden is also available for wedding ceremonies.",
          "C": "Vegetarian meals are also one of our specialties.",
          "D": "It is prohibited to take photos anywhere in the center."
        },
        "answer": "B"
      },
      {
        "question": "blank 3",
        "option": {
          "A": "cookers",
          "B": "chefs",
          "C": "chiefs",
          "D": "customers"
        },
        "answer": "B"
      },
      {
        "question": "blank 4",
        "option": {
          "A": "image",
          "B": "imagine",
          "C": "imaginary",
          "D": "imaginable"
        },
        "answer": "D"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "part6_004",
    "title": "Service Interruption Notice",
    "content": "Questions 1 through 4. refer to the following notice.  \n\nDear Customer, \n\nEarly tomorrow moring, our Internet banking facility will be offline for maintenance. We expect it to be down from around 2 AM, and the __1.__ will be up four hours. This is necessary if we are to fulfill an ongoing mission to provide our customers with the best possible online experience/ __2.__. \n\nCustomers requiring emergency bankung services can still use telephone banking. Telephone numbers for telephone banking can be found on the UFS website, which will otherwise remain operational. ATM machines, too, will not be affected __3.__ the disruption. ATM transaction fees will be waived throughout this period as a compensatory measure. We sincerely __4.__ for any inconvenience caused. \n\nThank you for banking with United Fiscal Services.",
    "questions": [
    {
        "question": "blank 1",
        "option": {
          "A": "duration",
          "B": "during",
          "C": "durable",
          "D": "durability"
        },
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "question": "blank 2",
        "option": {
          "A": "Services will resume at 6 AM.",
          "B": "Press two for credit card services.",
          "C": "Online banking has been canceled permanently.",
          "D": "Please contact customer service for a full refund."
        },
        "answer": "A"
      },
      {
        "question": "blank 3",
        "option": {
          "A": "of",
          "B": "as",
          "C": "to",
          "D": "by"
        },
        "answer": "D"
      },
      {
        "question": "blank 4",
        "option": {
          "A": "delight",
          "B": "apologize",
          "C": "satisfy",
          "D": "acquire"
        },
        "answer": "B"
      }
    ]
  }
]

